老爸老妈的罗漫史\n第1季 第11集
How.I.Met.Your.Mother\nSeason 01 Episode 11
孩子们,新年夜总是很烂
Kids,the thing about New Year's Eve is that it sucks.
当然, 在电视上看好象还不错
Sure,it looks great on TV,
但在现实里, 通常会让人失望
but in reality,it's always just a big letdown,
2005年, 我试图挑战一下惯例
but in 2005,I attempted to do the impossible,
让我的朋友们过一个很棒的新年夜
to give my friends a great New Year's Eve.
我也有个主意
I had an idea of how to do it,too
但代价是花去一半的圣诞奖金
and all it cost was half my christmas bonus.
不错，那就是Limo（林肯的一款车型）
that's right-- a Limo.
噢,天, Ted 这太棒了
Oh,man,Ted,this is great.
好了, 伙计们, 我们讨论下计划
Okay,people,let's talk strategy.
去年我们最后都各走各的,这样很糟糕
Last new years,we went our separate ways,\nand it sucked.
今年我们要么一起去派对,要么哪也别去
This year we party together or not at all.
我筛选了你们的派对建议
Now,I sifted through your party submissions
缩小到了5个
and I narrowed them down to these five.
有问题?
Question?
嗯, Barney, 你的建议我们收到了，但是……
Yes,Barney,your submissions were received and no,
别想我们会穿着你的内裤去任何派对
we will not be attending any parties\nin your pants.
但我发的电子贺卡你很享受, 是不?
but you enjoyed the e-vite,right?
那可真是我内裤的照片哦
That was an actual picture of my pants.
我们要在午夜前去这5个派对
We will hit all five parties before midnight,
然后选出一个
and then narrow them down to one,
纽约最棒的派对
the most awesome party in New York city,
我们就在那迎接新年钟声,还有在新的一年里
and that is where we will ring,nay rock,
狂欢
in the new year.
好了, 1号派对
All right,and party number one,
我们会在那见到Mary Beth?
that's where we get to meet Mary Beth?
Mary Beth?\nMary Beth?
她在我办公室工作
she works in my office,
她好象对我有点感觉
she seems like she might be into me.
老是找理由抱我
She's always finding reasons to hug me.
所以今晚我们将看到...
So tonight we'll see...
人们总是问我
people often ask me,
"Barney, 为什么你总是这么这么有激情?"
"Barney,how is it that you're so psyched so much of the time?"
谁? 谁会这样问你?
By who? Who asks you that?
答案就在这
and the answer is right here
我的, 私人珍藏"充满激情" 合辑
my own,personal "get psyched" mix.
人们都认为一张好的合辑应该跌宕起伏
No people often think a good mix should\nrise and fall,
但大家都错了
but people are wrong.
应该全是高潮才对, 宝贝
It should be all rise,baby.
准备好
Now prepare yourselves
开始一趟刺激的音频之旅
for an audio journey into the white-hot center of adrenaline.
这真的有用
it's working.
我兴奋起来了
I am definitely getting psyched.
噢, 天 我已经在危险的边缘了
Oh,god.I'm reaching dangerous levels of psychage.
得扮机器人了
Must do robot.
我们来吧!
let's do this!
- 好!\n- 来吧!
-Yes!\n-Let's!
司机?
driver?
大家好!
Hello!
Ranjit!\nRanjit!
伙计, 你在开Limo
Dude,you're driving a Limo now.
太棒了
That's awesome.
我搬到现实世界里来啦
I've moved up in the world.
你们怎么认识的?
How do you guys know each other?
有次我们一起进了出租车
We rode in his cab one time.
很长的故事
It's a long story.
我们还在等什么?
what are we waiting for?
有5个派对等着我们去\n而且还是得在3小时之内
We got five parties to hit,\nand three hours to do it.
我真希望我能和你们一起
I wish I could come with you guys
但Derek可能马上就来接我了
but Derek should be coming by any minute\nto pick me up.
Robin要和她男朋友Derek共度新年夜
Robin was spending new year's eve with her boyfriend,Derek.
Derek\nDerek.
他似乎有钱, 有事业, 有样貌
He was like rich, successful,handsome.
我讨厌那家伙
I hated that guy.
我会想你们的
I'll miss you guys.
玩的开心点
Have fun.
拜
Bye.
明年见
See ya next year.
去找他吧
Go get him.
这有点糟
this kind of sucks.
好了, 别失望
Okay,nobody get down.
我们知道会这样
We knew this going in.
我们已经有一位“牺牲”了
We're a man down.
这只是代表我们要去派对玩的更猛
That just means we're gonna have to party that much harder.
Ranjit! 1号派对
Ranjit! Party number one.
1号派对!
Party number one!
1号派对!!
Party number one!!
不敢相信我们从有小猪的派对离开了
I can't believe we're leaving a party that\nhad pigs in blankets.
如果你们觉得我们能击中
If you think we can beat that,
可以得到个铜的
you got some brass ones.
我们还得去4个派对
we've got four more parties to hit.
如果1号派对是最棒的
If party number one turns out to be the best,
我们只要坐着Limo回来就好了
we'll just Limo on back to it.
我们还没正式认识
We didn't really get a chance to meet.
我是Lily, 这是我的未婚夫, Marshall
I'm Lily,and this is my fiance,Marshall.
Mary Beth\nMary Beth.
很高兴认识你们
So great to meet you guys.
我也想这么说
My word.
你, 你真友好
You're,you're friendly.
大家好, Barney的美国派对朋友们
Hello,American party friends of Barney'	s.
噢，不\nOh，no
那么, Barney, 介绍下你的新朋友?
so,Barney,who's your new friend?
Natalya\nNatalya.
噢, 真友好
Oh,friendly.
嗯, 你从哪来, Natalya?
So,where are you from,Natalya?
她... 谁知道?
She... who knows?
前苏联喝翻屁股阿斯坦?
The former soviet republic of\ndrunk-off-her-ass-istan?
醉酒狂想?
Super-drunk-fantastic?
她很棒吧?
Isn't she awesome?
你的脚怎么了, 宝贝?
How are your feet doing,baby?
嗯, 我喜欢这双鞋
Okay,I love these shoes,
但是我化疼痛为激情的机率比较小
but the pain-to-hotness ratio is pretty steep.
我们能去一趟公寓让我顺便换双鞋吗?
Can we swing by the apartment,so I can change?
拜托, Lily, 我们面前的是\n一个行程紧密的狂欢之夜
Come on,Lily,we have a tightly scheduled evening of awesomeness ahead of us.
我要你用精神力量克服疼痛
I need you to power through the pain.
好吧, Ted, 但这些小狗真的会乱叫
Okay,Ted,but these dogs are really barking.
是真的 我能听到
It's true. I can hear them.
怎么了, 小伙子们?
What's that,little boys?
怎么了?
What's that?
你想去... 狂欢?
You wanna go for a... rock?
Ranjit! 2号派对
Ranjit!Party number two.
2号派对
Party number two.
2号派对?
Party number two?
没那么棒
Not so good.
我们回1号派对吧
Let's go back to party number one.
不行, 不能回头
No,no turning back.
Ranjit, 3号派对
Ranjit,party number three.
3号派对
Party number three.
等等, 等等
wait,wait,wait.
我们得转头
We have to turn around.
我们丢了Natalya
We left Natalya.
Barney, 我们没谁真的喜欢她
Barney,none of us really liked her.
什么?!
What?!
抱歉
Sorry.
很好, Lily
very nice,Lily.
你知道, 她是这个国家的客人
You know,she is a guest in this country.
如果你们背身不理她
So while you may chose to turn your back on her,
我则决定正面与她“相迎”
I choose to turn my front on her.
怎么样?
What up?
我为Barney感到抱歉
I'm sorry about Barney.
别, 我玩的很开心
No,I'm having a great time.
我很高兴你今晚邀我出来
I'm really glad that you asked me out tonight.
我也是
Me,too.
嗨, Robin
Hi,Robin.
Ted, Derek放我鸽子了
Ted,Derek stood me up.
Derek\nDerek.
今晚我们行程很紧
Now,we had a tight schedule to keep that night
而且我已经和另外一个女孩约会了
and I was already on a date with another girl.
但...是Robin
But...it was Robin.
Ranjit, 转头
Ranjit,turn it around.
天, 我很抱歉
God,I'm so sorry about this.
你们有你们的行程,而我把它搞乱了
You guys had your schedule and\nI screwed it all up.
不, 这很完美
No,this is perfect.
这是注定的
It's meant to be.
我们全聚在一起了
We're all back togeer.
发生什么了?
What happened?
Derek在康涅狄格州的生意没谈完
Derek's stuck in Connecticut closing some deal.
谁会在新年夜工作?
Who works on New Year's Eve?
好吧
Okay.
现在感觉更糟了
Now I feel worse.
我本来很期待今晚的
I was really looking forward to this night.
这太糟糕了
This sucks.
伙计,不是现在!
dude,not now!
什么? 她需要点激情
What?She needs to get psyched.
Barney\nBarney.
好吧
Fine.
也许我该回家算了
Maybe I should just go home.
Barney!\nBarney!
我手滑了
My finger slipped.
听着, Robin, 你不会回家
Look,Robin,you're not going home.
拜托, 今天是新年夜
Come on,it's New Year's Eve.
听着, 你的伴没了
Look,so your date fell through.
那又怎样?
So what?
你要有人约会是为什么?
What do you need a date for?
在午夜可以亲吻的人?
Someone to kiss at midnight?
那好, 我可以在...
Fine,I'll kiss you at...
午夜过后一点亲你
a little bit after midnight.
嗨, 我是Robin
Hi,I'm Robin.
Mary Beth\nMary Beth.
你真友善
You're friendly.
我还没吃过饭
I haven't eaten dinner yet.
有什么可以吃的吗?
Is there anything to eat in this thing?
就这个了
That's it.
我知道你想吃什么
I know what you're jonesing for.
Ranjit, 带我们去Gray's Papaya（快餐店）!
Ranjit,take us to gray's papaya!
耶 Ted, 你真棒
yes.Ted,you rock.
我们不能回头找Natalya
We couldn't go back for Natalya,
没时间找一个人\n但是我们就有时间去吃热狗?
a human being,but we do have time for hot dogs?
我们喜欢热狗
we like hot dogs.
不 不
No. No.
我们已经落后行程了
We are already behind schedule.
Ted, 拜托
Ted,come on.
我们只有一个半小时就到午夜了
We have an hour and a half before midnight
我可不想亲Ranjit
I don't want to be kissing Ranjit.
你不知道你错过了什么
You don't know what you're missing.
拜托, 只是20分钟的路
Come on,it's only a 20-minute detour.
我正好需要这么多时间
Which is exactly how much time I need.
Ranjit, 停车
Ranjit,stop the car.
停车
Stopping the car.
等等 宝贝, 你要干嘛?
Wait.Baby,what are you doing?
我要回家
I'm going home.
什么? 别!
What? No!
我不能继续受这双鞋的煎熬了,我就是忍不了
I can't stay in these heels any longer,\nI just can't.
有辆出租车在那
There's a cab over there.
我冲回家然后换鞋
I'll just run back to the apartment and change shoes.
但...热狗
But...hot dogs.
我知道, 宝贝, 我也想去
I know,baby,I'd love to go,
但是现在是两个对一个
but it's two against one.
好吧, 我和你一起去
Okay,I'll go with you.
不用了, 宝贝
No,baby.
Baby, 你和他们一起我会去...
Baby,you go with them and I'll meet you at,at...
3号派对找你们
party number three.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
如果我没见到你, 先说新年快乐
If I don't see you,Happy New Year.
别说这个
Don't say that.
我们会找到对方的
We'll find each other.
我知道我们会
I know we will.
- 拜, Lil\n- 拜
-By,Lil.\n-Bye.
多好的女人
Hell of a woman.
我们去买热狗吧!
Let's go get some hot dogs!
Ranjit, 3号派对
Ranjit,party number three.
3号派对
Party number three.
看看我们
Look at us.
坐着Limo
Riding around in a Limo.
吃着热狗
Eating hot dogs.
待遇和总统差不多了
It's like we're the president.
我打赌你现在感觉好多了
I'll bet you're feeling better now.
好多了
so much better.
那是Moby吗?
Is that Moby?
我想那是Moby
I think that that's Moby.
好了, 孩子们, 我们小时候Moby是流行唱片艺人
Now,kids,Moby was a popular recording artist\nwhen I was young.
不是吧
No way.
那真是Moby
That's totally Moby.
太棒了
That's awesome.
我该说点什么吗?
Should I say something?
我得说点什么, 对不?
I should say something,right?
Moby!\nMoby!
嘿, Moby!
Hey,Moby!
噢, 我的天 他走过来了
Oh,my god. He's coming over.
大家酷点
Everybody be cool.
你好
Hello.
怎么了?
What's up?
你, 要去什么地方吗?
you,going somewhere?
我只是去闹区的派对
I'just going to this party downtown.
想搭便车吗?
You want a ride?
好吧
Sure.
欢迎
Welcome.
嗯
Right.
你真友好
You're friendly.
超级歌迷
Big fan.
Barney Stinson\nBarney Stinson.
嗯, ...
So,...
那个派对怎么样?
what about this party?
只是新年的那些
It's just a New Year's thing.
你知道, 和一些朋友
You know,with some friends.
听起来很不错
that sounds awesome.
你们想一起来吗?
You guys want to come?
我们很乐意
we'd love to.
好啊
All right.
Ted\nTed.
悄悄话?
Sidebar?
Moby, 换一下, 行吗?
Moby,switch up,will you?
Moby\nMoby.
怎么了?
what's up?
Lily怎么办?
What about Lily?
给她打电话
Call her.
我有给她打电话
I've been trying to call her.
但打不通
I can't get through.
全是线路忙
All the circuits are jammed.
这就是新年夜
That's New Year's Eve for you.
嗯, 我们可以先去一会儿\nMoby的派对然后...
look,we'll just swing by Moby's party and\nthen afterwards...
不, 我-我不行 Lily等着在
no,I-I can't. Lily's waiting.
我得...
I gotta...
我得去找她
I gotta find her.
好吧, 我们在3号派对见
Okay,I'll meet you at party number three.
但...
But...
拜托! Moby的派对!
come on!Moby's party!
Moby的派对!
Moby's party!
Moby的派...
Moby's par...
Ranjit\nRanjit.
Moby的派对
Moby's party.
这合辑很酷
This is a cool mix.
你知道, 人们认为一张好的合辑应该跌宕起伏
You know,people think a great mix has\nto rise and fall.
我觉得应该全是高潮
I think it should be all rise.
就是
Yes.
Moby...\nMoby...
应该激烈的开始, 然后更加猛烈
it should start high,get higher.
这张合辑是我的骄傲
This mix is my pride and joy.
我从来没有离开过它
I never leave home without it.
就象我对Janice的感情一样
that's how I feel about Janice here.
所以我就说我到的时候你的摩托车就那样了
so I said,your motorcycle was like that when I got here."
你不是Moby, 你是吗?
you're not Moby,are you?
谁?
Who?
Moby\nMoby
唱片艺人, Moby
the recording artist,Moby.
不是
No.
但我们说"嘿, Moby"时
But when we said "hey,Moby,"
你说, "耶"
you said,"yeah."
我以为你说的是 "Tony"
I thought you said "Tony."
所以你是叫Tony?
So your name is Tony?
不是
No.
我们到了
we're here.
好了
All right.
你们要来吗?
You guys are gonna come in?
你确定?
You sure?
来吧 里面疯狂极了
Come on.It's going to get nuts in there.
有个家伙欠我钱
There's this dude who owes me money.
不了, 我们还好
no,we're good.
我们还好
We're good.
新年快乐, 假Moby
Happy New Year,not Moby.
嘿，注意安全
be safe.
为什么我们会觉得那家伙是Moby?
why did we think that guy was Moby?
不知道
I don't know.
我看到个短平头的时髦家伙
I see a short bald hipster,
就马上想到Moby了
my mind goes straight to Moby.
是Marshall的电话
that's Marshall's phone.
- 喂\n- Marshall, 感谢上帝我终于打通了
- Hey...\n- Marshall,thank god I got through.
嘿, 小心肝
Hey,sexy.
Barney, Marshall呢?
Barney,where's Marshall?
他把电话丢在Limo上了
He left his phone in the Limo.
他去找你了
He's out looking for you.
什么? 哪儿?
What? Where?
3号派对
Party number three.
我就在3号派对这啊...
I'm here at party number three and...
噢, 我的天!
oh,my god!
猜谁走进来了
Guess who just walked in--
- Moby!\n- Moby?!\n- Moby!\n- Moby?!
她在楼上
She's upstairs.
Lily, 你现在就赶快出来
Lily,you have to get out of there this instant.
那不是Moby
That's not Moby.
不, 我知道Moby还有...
no,I know Moby and that's Mo...
他有枪吗?
does he have a gun?
快跑!
Run!
噢, 我的天
Oh,my god,
假Moby的派对就是4号派对
not Moby's party is party number four.
真是巧了?
What are the odds?
那个家伙是谁?!
who was that guy?!
我们只知道他不是Moby也不是Tony
we know it's not Moby and it's not Tony.
Ranjit, 开车!
Ranjit,drive!
去哪?
Where to?
3号派对!
Party number three!
3号派对
Party number three.
不对, 我刚就在3号派对啊
no,but I was just at party number three.
不, 不, 不对, 你刚才是在4号派对
No,no,no,no you were at party number four.
你一定是看错单子了
You must have looked at the list wrong.
在经历过如此不愉快的事情后
after that rather unpsyching experience,
你们知道现在该干什么了吗?
you know what it's time for?
现在是... 什么?
It's time to... what?
对了, 重振激情时间
That's right,re-psych.
重...
Re-psy...
糟糕!
suck!
噢, 我的天那!
Oh,my god!
假Moby把我的"充满激情" 合辑拿走了!
Not Moby took my "get psyched" mix!
Barney, Barney, Barney\nBarney,Barney,Barney,
不值得!
it's not worth it!
我们走吧
Let it go.
我们回到行程表来
We need to get back on schedule.
啊, 难缠的家伙
Oh,nuts.
Ranjit, 你确定我不能帮忙吗?
Ranjit,are you sure I can't help?
确定
No.
我遇到难题了（暗指我在尿尿）
I am pissed.
Ted, 我不想你看到我遇到难题\n（不想你看到我尿尿）
Ted,I don't want you to see me pissed.
好的
Okay.
Okay, 没什么问题
Okay,not a problem.
他会把车升起来
He'll jack it up,
换轮胎
slap on a tire
我们会准时到达3号派对
and we'll be at party number three in no time.
希望Marshall会打电话来
I wish Marshall would call.
我猜是线路忙
I guess the circts are jammed.
你知道为什么线路忙吗
you know why all the circuits are jammed
因为所有的人都在给爱人打电话
because everyone's calling their loved ones,
全世界的人
everyone around the world.
除了Barney
Everyone except Barney.
好, 笑吧
sure,laugh.
嘲笑Barney Stinson吧
Laugh for Barney Stinson.
嘲笑可悲的小丑
Laugh for the sad clown
被困在旋转马车上,有西装雪茄女人烈酒
trapped on his whirling carousel of suits\nand cigars and bimbos and booze.
转啊转
Round and rod it goes.
是转去哪呢?
And where's it all heading?
哪里也不是
Nowhere.
这样只是因为你丢了"充满激情" 合辑吗?
Is this just 'cause you lost your\n"get psyched" mix?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不能有忧郁的一面吗?
Am I not allowed to have a pensive side?
不 不, 今晚不行
No. No,not tonight.
在Limo里不行
Not in the Limo.
我们得保持激情
We got to stay psyched.
Ted花了很多心思让大家有个崭新的新年
Ted went to a lot of trouble to make this\nan awesome new year's.
Shothrough the heart\nShothrough the heart
and you're to blame,darling\nand you're to blame,darling
you give love a bad name\nyou give love a bad name
A bad name ha!\nA bad name ha!
I play my part and you played your game\nI play my part and you played your game
Darling,you give love a bad name,bad name!\nDarling,you give love a bad name,bad name!
没事的
It'll be fine.
我们马上就能出发了
We'll be out of here in a jiff.
Ted, 我得走了
Ted,I'm going to head out.
我的室友在附近有个派对
My roommates are having a party not far from here.
别
No.
听着, 我知道今晚和我计划的有点偏差, 但...
Look,I know this night isn't turning out\nthe way I planned,but...
你喜欢Robin多久了?
how long have you been in love with Robin?
我没有喜欢...
I'm not in love...
我们只是朋友
we're just friends.
你怎么会这么想?
Where are you getting that from?
Ted, 没关系
Ted,it's okay.
我没事
I'm fine.
而且我知道她也喜欢你
And I can tell that she's into you,too.
这太滑稽了
That's ridiculous.
等下 真的吗?
Wait.Really?
新年快乐, Ted
Happy New Year,Ted.
我不敢相信Mary Beth在午夜前走掉了
I can't believe Mary Beth left before midnight.
她只是得去另一个派对
she just had to make an appearance at this other party.
没什么大不了的
It's no big deal.
我第一次坐Limo是五岁的时候
The first time I rode in a Limo I was five.
在去祖父葬礼的路上
I was on the way to my grandfather's funeral.
我想, 在某一方面, 我仍然在
I suppose,in a way,I still am.
好了, 这里变的太奇怪了
Okay,it's getting weird in here.
我要去给Marshall打电话
I'm going to call Marshall.
但他把手机丢车里了
But he left his phone.
Marshall! Marshall!\nMarshall! Marshall!
我为你的女伴感到抱歉
I'm sorry about your girl.
你的男伴也是
Sorry about your guy.
至少我们在午夜都有人亲吻
at least we both have someone to kiss at midnight.
你忘了我们的小约定了吗?
Did you forget about our little deal?
我还没有忘
Because I did not.
我也没有
I did not,too.
Derek\nDerek.
工作怎么样了?
How's work?
给你私人空间
I'll give you some privacy.
Marshall!\nMarshall!
好吧,  旅行计划怎么样?
Okay,how's this for a plan?
我们现在就开始步行
We start walking now,
12:45就可以到3号派对了
we get to party number three by 12:45.
我们在中央标准时间庆祝新年
We celebrate the new year in central standard time
Marshall!\nMarshall!
算了吧, Ted
Give it a rest,Ted.
什么算了?
Give what a rest?
试着让今晚变的不同寻常
Trying to turn this night into anything more\nthan what it is,
新年夜是单身汉们
which is New Year's Eve which is he single biggest
每年最郁闷的时候
letdown of a night every single year.
Marshall!\nMarshall!
拜托, 来吧, 我们还可以回头
Come on,come on,we can still turn\nthis thing around.
我们还有10分钟
We've still got ten minutes.
别在试着追求什么魔法般的完美新年了, Ted
Stop trying to chase down some magical,\nperfect New Years,Ted.
不会发生的
It doesn't exist.
Marshall!\nMarshall!
Lily!\nLily!
天
Holy crap.
Marshall!\nMarshall!
Lily!\nLily!
我就知道我最终会碰到你们
I knew I'd catch up with you guys eventually.
太多要说了
So much to tell.
我在3号派对上找不到Lily所以就...
I couldn't find Lily at party number three\nso I walked...
走到4号派对去了
I walked to the next party on the list.
假Moby的派对?
Not Moby's party?
是啊, Moby的派对
Yes,Moby's party.
看他在我衬衫上签名了
Check it out He signed my shirt.
再猜我找到了什么
And guess what I found.
我听到派对上在放这个
I heard it playing at the party,
所以我把它偷回来了
so I swiped it.
- Marshall...\n- Marshall...\n- I know.
- 我知道 我知道
- 来吧\n- 来吧!
-Come on.\n-Come on!
宝贝, 宝贝, 我好担心你
Baby,baby,I was so worried about you.
为什么不给我打电话?
Why didn't you call me?
我试过了, 宝贝
I tried,baby.
线路全是繁忙
All the circuits were jammed.
等等, 还有
But wait,there's more.
离开4号派对
After party number four,
我猜你们一定去了5号派对
I figured you guys went to party number five.
所以我也去了5号派对
And so I went there,too,
而且那里很棒
and it is awesome.
我都想哭了, 那里真的很棒
I want to cry,it is so awesome.
我们得去那
We have to go there.
怎么去? 我们找不到出租车
How?We'll never get a cab.
车胎修好了
The flat's fixed.
我们去吧!
Let's do this!
来吧! 上车!
Come on!In!
走, 走, 走!
Go,go,go!
Natalya?\nNatalya?
她一直在前排座位上睡觉
it turns out she was asleep in the front seat the whole time.
Ranjit, 为什么不告诉我?
Ranjit,why didn't you tell me?
我不想吵醒她
I didn't want to wake her.
她看起来如此平静
She looked so peaceful.
5号派对离这里有20个街区
Party number five is 20 blocks away
在城市的另一边
and all the way across town.
Ranjit, 你能让我们8分钟内到吗?
Ranjit,can you get us there in eight minutes?
6分钟就可以了
I get you there in six.
我想我做不到了
I don't think I can do it.
不! 拜托!
No! Come on!
快开, 蠢出租车!
Move,you stupid taxi!
只有3分钟了!
Three minutes!
拜托!
Come on!
Ranjit, 熄火吧
Ranjit,put her in park.
伙计们, 我相信5号派对很棒
Dudes,I'm sure party number five is awesome,
但它不是纽约最棒的派对
but it's not the best party in New York.
因为这才是, 就在这
'Cause this is,right here.
干杯 说的好
Cheers.Well said.
- 干杯\n- 干杯
-Cheers.\n-Cheers.
就这样
And just like that,
我们有了那个完美的新年夜
we were having the perfect New Year's Eve.
好笑的是,我花了一整晚时间……
The funny thing is all night long,
试图去追求一些东西
I'd been trying to chase something down
结果就在Limo里
that was right there in that Limo.
Derek?!\nDerek?!
Derek\nDerek.
上来吧
come on in.
Robin\nRobin.
我加快了会议进程
I cut my meeting short
因为我想在午夜见到你
because I wanted to see you at midnight.
我不敢相信你做到了
I can't believe you made it.
我做到了, 宝贝
I made it,baby.
我超级爱你, 可以不?
I super love you,okay?
拿着, 你需要薄荷
Here,you need a mint
新年快乐!
Happy New Year!
故事讲到这里你们可能会为你们的老爸感到遗憾
You probably want to feel bad for your old man at this point in the story.
但不需要
Well,don't.
不是每个夜晚都有美好的结局
Not every night has a happy ending.
但每个夜晚都是很重要的
But all of it's important.
所有的夜晚都都让我们前进
All of it was leading somewhere.
因为突然
Because suddenly,
就是2006年了
it was 2006.
2006是很重要的一年
And 2006 was a big one.
Ted!\nTed!
怎么了, 伙计?
What the hell,man?
我想我们有约定
I thought we had a deal.
你的伴怎么办?
What about your guy?
现在是午夜
It's midnight.
去亲他啊
Go kiss him.
他让我等他
he kept me waiting.
我也可以让他等我
I can keep him waiting.
约定就是约定
a deal is a deal.
新年快乐
Happy New Year.
老爸老妈浪漫史 第一季 第十一集
How.I.Met.Your.Mother\nSeason 01 Episode 11